== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Sheldon:)Leonard, I've been
meaning to ask you:
(Sheldon:)what size shoe
do you wear?
(Leonard:)Why?
(Sheldon:)I'm trying to take
more of an interest
(Sheldon:)in other
people's lives.
(Leonard:)That's nice.
(Leonard:)I wear a size
eight and a half.
(Sheldon:)That's small.
(Sheldon:)So, tell me, do you have
any plans for the weekend?
(Leonard:)Are you gonna laugh
at the answer?
(Sheldon:)Only if the answer is
"shopping for baby shoes."
(Leonard:)If you must know,
(Leonard:)Penny won a spa weekend
from work
(Leonard:)and she's taking me.
(Sheldon:)Oh, well you know,
that is interesting.
(Sheldon:)I wonder what kind of infection
you'll come home with.
(Sheldon:)My money's on fungal.
They're still having girl''
night across the hall.
Oh, so, hang out with me
and we'll have boys' night.
(Sheldon:)At our age,
(Sheldon:)why don't we call it
man's night?
(Leonard:)Because we just spent our
allowance on comic books.